Guide to the Democratic Socialists of America Records TAM.105
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VI. Conventions, 1971-2007; 12.33 Linear Feet in 23 manuscript boxes, 3 flat boxes, and 3 folders in 2 shared boxes; 25 audiocassettes; 2 Hi8; 18 VHS; 3.72 Gigabytes in 144 computer files
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Unidentified Convention Materials, undated (Box 308, Folder 5)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) and New American Movement (NAM) -- Unity Convention, March 1982 (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - Unity Celebration -- Berkeley, August 1982 (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - Socialist Scholars Conference -- "What's Left?", April 1983 (Box 125, Folder 7, Box Shared Tamiment 174, Folder 18)
  - Democratic Socialists of America -- First Convention, October 1983 (Box 126, Folder 1-4, Box 127, Folder 1)
  - Socialist Scholars Conference -- "The Encounter with America", April 1984 (Box 127, Folder 2)
  - Socialist Scholars Conference -- "The Left in Crisis", April 1985 (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - Democratic Socialists of America National Convention, November 1985 (Box 127, Folder 4-6)
  - Socialist Scholars Conference -- "Resistance, Rebellion and Revolt", April 1986 (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - Socialist Scholars Conference -- "Against Domination: State, Class, Race, Gender", April 1987 (Box 128, Folder 2)
  - Democratic Socialists of America National Convention, December 1987
    - Correspondence, Schedules, Program, and Flyers (Box 128, Folder 3-5)
    - Video Recording (Box 158, Vhs 105.0159)
  - Socialist Scholars Conference -- "Socialist Movements: National and International", April 1988 (Box 128, Folder 6)
  - Democratic Socialists of America Board Meeting -- "Changing America: The First Hundred Days and Beyond", November 1988 (Box 128, Folder 7)
  - Socialist Scholars Conference -- "The Two Centuries of Revolution: 1789-1989", April 1989 (Box 128, Folder 8, Box Shared Tamiment 174, Folder 18)
  - Democratic Socialists of America National Convention, November 1989 (Box 129, Folder 1-3)
  - Democratic Socialists of America National Convention -- Barbara Ehrenreich -- Keynote, November 1989
    - Video Recording (Box 159, Vhs 105.0166)
    - Video Recording (Box 163, Vhs 105.0213)
  - Socialist Scholars Conference -- "Democratic Upheavals and the End of the Cold War", April 1990 (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - Democratic Socialists of America Board Meeting -- "A World Transformed: Socialism and the Triumph of Democracy", November 1990 (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - Democratic Socialists of America National Convention -- Bogdan Denitch and Joanne Borkon Session, 1990 (Box 163, Vhs 105.0212)
  - Socialist Scholars Conference -- "After the Flood: The World Transformed", April 1991
    - Programs, Flyers, and Correspondence (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - Audio Recording (Box 164, Audiocassette 105.0221)
    - Audio Recording (Box 164, Audiocassette 105.0222)
  - Democratic Socialists of America National Convention and Leadership School, November 1991
    - Flyers, Correspondence, and Programs (Box 130, Folder 1-3)
    - Audio Recording (Box 155, Audiocassette 105.0106)
    - Audio Recording (Box 155, Audiocassette 105.0107)
    - Audio Recording (Box 155, Audiocassette 105.0109)
    - Video Recording (Box 159, Vhs 105.0168)
    - Video Recording (Box 162, Vhs 105.0202)
  - Socialist Scholars Conference -- "What's Left? Whose New World Order?", April 1992 (Box 130, Folder 4)
  - Socialist Scholars Conference -- "The Post Cold War and the Global Crises: The United States, North America, and the World", April 1993 (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - Democratic Socialists of America National Convention, November 1993
    - Correspondence, Flyers, and Programs (Box 135, Folder 2-3)
    - Audio Recording (Box 164, Audiocassette 105.0223)
    - Audio Recording (Box 164, Audiocassette 105.0224)
    - Audio Recording (Box 164, Audiocassette 105.0225)
    - Audio Recording (Box 164, Audiocassette 105.0226)
    - Audio Recording (Box 164, Audiocassette 105.0227)
    - Audio Recording (Box 164, Audiocassette 105.0228)
    - Audio Recording (Box 164, Audiocassette 105.0229)
    - Audio Recording (Box 164, Audiocassette 105.0230)
    - Audio Recording (Box 164, Audiocassette 105.0231)
    - Audio Recording (Box 164, Audiocassette 105.0232)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_98
  - Democratic Socialists of America National Convention -- Breaking Bread and Women in Politics Awards, November 1993
    - Video Recording (Box 156, Vhs 105.0131)
    - Video Recording (Box 159, Vhs 105.0167)
  - Socialist Scholars Conference -- "The Chickens Come Home to Roost: The Price of Neoliberalism", April 1994
    - Correspondence, Flyers, and Programs (Box 135, Folder 4)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_99
  - Socialist Scholars Conference -- "The Global Economy…and the Future of Democracy" and "The Legacy of Malcolm X", April 1995
    - Correspondence, Flyers, and Programs (Box 135, Folder 5)
    - Audio Recording (Box 164, Audiocassette 105.0233)
    - Audio Recording (Box 164, Audiocassette 105.0234)
    - Audio Recording (Box 164, Audiocassette 105.0235)
    - Audio Recording (Box 164, Audiocassette 105.0236)
    - Audio Recording (Box 164, Audiocassette 105.0237)
  - Democratic Socialists of America National Convention, November 1995
    - Correspondence, Flyers, and Programs (Box 135, Folder 6, Box 136, Folder 1-3)
    - Audio Recording (Box 155, Audiocassette 105.0099)
    - Audio Recording (Box 155, Audiocassette 105.0100)
    - Audio Recording (Box 155, Audiocassette 105.0101)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_100
  - Socialist Scholars Conference -- "Two Cheers for Utopia: Reimagining Socialism", April 1996 (Box 136, Folder 4)
  - Socialist Scholars Conference -- "Radical Alternatives on the Eve of the Millennium", April 1997 (Box 136, Folder 5)
  - Democratic Socialists of America National Convention, November 1997
    - Correspondence, Flyers, and Programs (Box 136, Folder 6, Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_101
  - Democratic Socialists of America National Convention -- Awards Dinner, November 1997 (Box 159, Vhs 105.0164)
  - Socialist Scholars Conference -- "A World to Win: From the Manifesto to Organizing for Socialist Change", March 1998
    - Correspondence, Flyers, and Programs (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_102
  - Democratic Socialists of America Activist Convention, November 1998 (Box 137, Folder 3)
  - Socialist Scholars Conference -- "the freedom to work and think, the freedom to love and desire", April 1999 (Box 137, Folder 4)
  - Democratic Socialists of America National Convention, November 1999
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Flyers (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_103
  - Unidentified Conference Sessions, August 11, 2000
    - Video Recording (Box 155, Hi8 105.0122)
    - Video Recording (Box 155, Hi8 105.0123)
  - Socialist Scholars Conference -- "Rockin' the Boat: Building Coalitions for the New Century", March-April 2000 (Box 137, Folder 6)
  - Socialist Scholars Conference -- "Rebuilding the Left for the New Century", April 2001 (Box 137, Folder 7)
  - Democratic Socialists of America National Convention, November 2001
    - Correspondence, Flyers, and Programs (Box 137, Folder 8)
    - Video Recording (Box 158, Vhs 105.0154)
    - Video Recording (Box 158, Vhs 105.0155)
    - Video Recording (Box 158, Vhs 105.0156)
    - Video Recording (Box 158, Vhs 105.0157)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_104
  - Socialist Scholars Conference -- "After 9/11: New Politics for Social Movements and the Left", April 2002 (Box 137, Folder 9)
  - Low Wage Economy Conference, September 2002
    - Video Recording (Box 159, Vhs 105.0172)
    - Video Recording (Box 159, Vhs 105.0173)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_105
  - Socialist Scholars Conference -- "War Without End? The Left Responds", March 2003
    - Program (Box 137, Folder 10)
    - Video Recording, TW_TAM_105_ER_223
  - "The War at Home: Organizing for Economic and Social Justice" Conference -- Berkeley, April 2003; TW_TAM_105_ER_106
  - Democratic Socialists of America National Convention, November 2003
    - Programs and Brochure (Box 137, Folder 11)
    - Digital Photographs, TW_TAM_105_ER_240
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_107
  - Socialist Scholars Conference -- "The World Is Not for Sale: Rethinking the Common Good", March 2004
    - Program (Box 137, Folder 12)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_108
  - Left Forum, April 2005; TW_TAM_105_ER_109
  - Democratic Socialists of America National Convention, November 2005 (Box 137, Folder 13)
  - Democratic Socialists of America National Convention, 2006 (Box 342, Folder 1)
  - Democratic Socialists of America National Convention, November 2007 (Box 137, Folder 14)
  - Democratic Socialists of America National Convention, 2009 (Box 342, Folder 2)
  - Democratic Socialists of America National Convention, 2011 (Box 342, Folder 3)
  - Democratic Socialists of America National Convention, 2013 (Box 342, Folder 4)
  - Democratic Socialists of America National Convention -- Resolutions, 2019 (Box 342, Folder 5)
  - Unidentified Conference Information, undated (Box 137, Folder 15)
  - Unidentified Conference Sessions, undated
    - Audio Recording (Box 155, Audiocassette 105.0108)
    - Audio Recording (Box 155, Audiocassette 105.0112)
    - Audio Recording (Box 155, Audiocassette 105.0113)
    - Video Recording (Box 159, Vhs 105.0169)
    - Video Recording (Box 159, Vhs 105.0170)
    - Video Recording (Box 159, Vhs 105.0171)
  - Unidentified Conference -- Opening Session and Industrial Democracy Session, undated (Box 165, Audiocassette 105.0264)
- Series VII. Publications, 1971-2013; 12.25 Linear Feet in 28 manuscript boxes; 6.01 Gigabytes in 377 computer files
  Arranged alphabetically by publication title.
  This series contains newsletters, journals, position papers, and pamphlets published by DSOC, NAM, and DSA. Committee publications, such as Green News, the Feminist Commission's Not Far Enough, Labor Voice, Nuestra Lucha, Religious Socialism, and YDSA publications, including The Activist, are included here. Also included are papers/bulletins on particular issues, (such as the importance of unions, education as a right, and women's health bibliographies), socialist bibliographies, guidelines, and glossaries (for example, "Glossary of Terms for Leftists"). "Incomplete" indicates that there is not a complete run of issues for a particular publication. A few unpublished writings also are included, as working papers. Published writing by Michael Harrington as a representative of DSOC, and later DSA, are included. All of these materials illustrate how DSA has communicated its message to its members and the general public over the years.
  Related Materials
  Past issues of outreach publications are available on DSA's website, archived copies of which are in Series XIV of the collection.
  - The Activist, 1984-March 1985 (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - The Activist, November 1985-January/February 1988 (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - The Activist, Summer 1988-September/October 1989 (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - The Activist -- Correspondence and Drafts, 1990-1991 (Box 138, Folder 4)
  - The Activist, Spring-Fall 1991 (Box 138, Folder 5)
  - The Activist, Spring-Fall 1992 (Box 138, Folder 6)
  - The Activist -- Correspondence and Drafts, 1992-1993 (Box 138, Folder 7)
  - The Activist, Spring-Summer 1993 (Box 138, Folder 8)
  - The Activist -- Correspondence, Drafts, and Issue, 1994 (Box 138, Folder 9)
  - The Activist, Summer and November 1995 (Box 138, Folder 10)
  - The Activist, January-September 1996 (Box 138, Folder 11)
  - The Activist, Spring 1997 (Box 138, Folder 12)
  - The Activist, Fall 1999-Fall 2000 (Box 138, Folder 13)
  - The Activist -- Grant Application and Summer Issue, 2001 (Box 138, Folder 14)
  - The Activist, Spring 2002 (Box 138, Folder 15)
  - The Activist, 2004
    - Notes, Correspondence, and Article (Box 138, Folder 16)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_120
  - The Activist -- Articles and Cover, 2010; TW_TAM_105_ER_119
  - Alternatives -- Drafts, Correspondence, and Issues -- Incomplete, 1986-1987 (Box 139, Folder 1-2)
  - Anti-Racism Commission Publications, 1977-1983
    - NAM, 1977-1981 (Box 308, Folder 6)
    - DSOC and DSA -- Anti-Racism, Latino, African American Commissions, 1978-1983 (Box 139, Folder 3)
  - Bibliographies and Literature Lists, circa 1973-1988, 1999
    - Paper Files (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_123
  - Days of Decision, November 1978 (Box 139, Folder 5)
  - Days of Decision -- Notes, Drafts, and Research, 1978-1979 (Box 139, Folder 6)
  - Days of Decision, Fall-Winter 1979-1980 (Box 139, Folder 7)
  - Days of Decision -- Correspondence, Drafts, and Research, 1980 (Box 139, Folder 8)
  - Days of Decision, Summer-December 1980 (Box 139, Folder 9)
  - Days of Decision -- Correspondence and Drafts, 1981 (Box 139, Folder 10)
  - Days of Decision, Spring and December 1981 (Box 139, Folder 11)
  - Days of Decision -- Correspondence and Drafts, 1982 (Box 139, Folder 12)
  - Days of Decision, Winter 1983-December 1984 (Box 139, Folder 13)
  - Days of Decision, 1985-1986 (Box 342, Folder 20)
  - Days of Decision, September 1985-Winter 1988 (Box 139, Folder 14)
  - Democratic Left -- Correspondence, Editorial Board Notes, and Research, 1972-1975 (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - The Newsletter of the Democratic Left, 1973-2023 (Box 342, Folder 22)
  - Democratic Left -- Correspondence, Drafts, and Research, 1976-1977 (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - The Newsletter of the Democratic Left, December 1977 (Box 140, Folder 3)
  - Democratic Left -- Correspondence, Drafts, Editorial Board Notes, and Research, 1978 (Box 140, Folder 4-5, Box 141, Folder 1)
  - The Newsletter of the Democratic Left and Plant Closings Special Report, March-April 1978 (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - Democratic Left -- Correspondence, Drafts, and Research, 1979 (Box 141, Folder 3)
  - Democratic Left -- Correspondence, Drafts, Editorial Board Minutes, and Research, 1980 (Box 141, Folder 4)
  - Democratic Left -- Correspondence, Drafts, Editorial Board Minutes, Photographs, and Research, 1981 (Box 141, Folder 5, Box 142, Folder 1-3)
  - Democratic Left -- Correspondence, Drafts, Editorial Board Minutes, and Research, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 4)
  - Democratic Left -- Correspondence, Drafts, Editorial Board Minutes, Photographs, and Research, 1983 (Box 143, Folder 1-3)
  - Democratic Left -- Correspondence, Drafts, Editorial Board Minutes, and Research, 1984 (Box 143, Folder 4)
  - Democratic Left -- Correspondence, Drafts, Editorial Board Minutes, and Research, 1985-1990 (Box 143, Folder 5)
  - Democratic Left -- Correspondence, Drafts, Editorial Board Minutes, and Research, 1991-1992 (Box 144, Folder 1)
  - Democratic Left -- Photographs, 1992-1996 (Box 144, Folder 2)
  - Democratic Left -- Correspondence, Drafts, Editorial Board Minutes, and Research, 1993 (Box 144, Folder 3)
  - Democratic Left, 1995-1997
    - Correspondence, Drafts, and Editorial Board Minutes (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_113
  - Democratic Left -- Correspondence, Drafts, and Editorial Board Minutes, 1998; TW_TAM_105_ER_114
  - Democratic Left -- Correspondence and Drafts, 1999; TW_TAM_105_ER_111
  - Democratic Left -- Correspondence and Drafts, 2000; TW_TAM_105_ER_112
  - Democratic Left -- Drafts, 2001; TW_TAM_105_ER_116
  - Democratic Left -- Draft, Meeting Minutes, and Report, 2002-2003; TW_TAM_105_ER_115
  - Democratic Left -- Drafts, 2005; TW_TAM_105_ER_117
  - Democratic Left -- Correspondence, 2015 (Box 342, Folder 21)
  - Democratic Socialists of America -- Background Papers and Political Perspectives, circa 1986-2009
    - Drafts and Final Publications (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_124
  - Democratic Socialists of America -- Working Papers on the Economy, circa 1982-1985 (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - Democratic Socialists of America -- Working Papers on the Economy, 1985-2003 (Box 145, Folder 2)
  - Democratic Socialists of America -- Brochures and Leaflets, circa 1982-2011
    - Drafts and Final Publications (Box 145, Folder 3-4)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_125
  - Democratic Socialists of America -- Directories, 1978-1989 (Box 145, Folder 5)
  - Democratic Socialists of America Local Organizing Manual, circa 1982-1993 (Box 145, Folder 6, Box 146, Folder 1)
  - Democratic Socialists of America Radio Project Newsletter, 1983 (Box 146, Folder 2)
  - Democratic Socialists of America Reports on Nicaragua, 1983 (Box 146, Folder 3)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee -- Background Paper, circa 1977 (Box 146, Folder 4)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee -- Brochures, circa 1976-1980 (Box 146, Folder 5)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee -- Harrington, Michael -- Capitalism, Socialism, and Energy, circa 1974-1975 (Box 146, Folder 6)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee -- Discussion Bulletins, 1973-1975 (Box 146, Folder 7)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee -- Discussion Bulletins, 1976-1979 (Box 146, Folder 8)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee -- Keynote Address by Michael Harrington at Fourth National Convention, February 1979 (Box 146, Folder 9)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee -- Harrington, Michael -- Say What You Mean--Socialism, 1974-1977 (Box 146, Folder 10)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee -- We Are the Socialists of the Democratic Left, 1973-1981 (Box 146, Folder 11)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee -- Harrington, Michael -- Welfare Capitalism in Crisis, December 1974 (Box 146, Folder 12)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee -- Working Papers and Reports, circa 1973-1978 (Box 146, Folder 13)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee -- Kohak, Erazim -- What Is Socialism?, circa 1974-1977 (Box 146, Folder 14)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee -- Howe, Irving -- The Near and the Far: What It Means to Be a Socialist in America Today, circa 1975-1978 (Box 146, Folder 15)
  - Environmental Commission Publications, 1987-1994 (Box 147, Folder 1)
  - Feminism and Socialism -- Statements and Papers, 1974-1981 (Box 147, Folder 2)
  - Harrington, Michael -- First Steps Toward a New Civilization, circa 1985-1986 (Box 147, Folder 3)
  - Health Care Activist, Fall 1991 (Box 147, Folder 4)
  - Health Commission Publications, 1972-1982
    - NAM, 1972-1978 (Box 309, Folder 12)
    - DSOC and DSA, 1978-1982 (Box 147, Folder 5)
  - Index to Articles on Occupational Safety and Health, 1979 (Box 147, Folder 6)
  - Institute of Democratic Socialism -- Pamphlets and Occasional Papers, 1977-1991 (Box 147, Folder 7)
  - Introduction to Democratic Socialism, 1989-1991 (Box 148, Folder 1)
  - Labor Activist, 1993-1996 (Box 148, Folder 2)
  - Labor Voice -- Incomplete, 1977-1989 (Box 148, Folder 3)
  - Letter to The New York Times by Robert Delson, April 1992 (Box 148, Folder 4)
  - Midwest Socialist, 2018 (Box 342, Folder 23)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Brochures, 1971-1980 (Box 148, Folder 5, Box 309, Folder 1)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Chalkboard, Winter 1973-1974 (Box 309, Folder 2)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Chapter Organizing Manuals, 1973-1977 (Box 148, Folder 6)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Coal Strike 1974: Economic Crisis and Political Promise, circa 1974-1975 (Box 309, Folder 3)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Community Strike Support: A Guide for the New American Movement, February 1972 (Box 309, Folder 4)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Convention Papers, 1975 (Box 148, Folder 7)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- The Cultural Gazette, Spring/Summer 1978 (Box 309, Folder 5)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Democratizing Education: Socialist Strategies for Campuses, June 1981 (Box 148, Folder 8)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Discussion Bulletin, 1977-1978, 1981
    - Drafts and Correspondence, 1977 (Box 309, Folder 6)
    - Drafts and Correspondence, 1978 (Box 309, Folder 7)
    - Drafts and Correspondence, 1981 (Box 309, Folder 8)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Kunnes, Rick (Editor) -- El Salvador: No Middle Ground, 1981 (Box 309, Folder 10)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Energy Commission Newsletter and Other Publications, 1974-1982 (Box 148, Folder 9, Box 309, Folder 11)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Film Guide, circa 1971-1972 (Box 148, Folder 10)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- A Guide to Strike Support, circa 1972 (Box 148, Folder 11)
  - New American Movement (NAM) and Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- Human Services Newsletter, Winter 1982 (Box 148, Folder 12)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- "Impeach Nixon" Bulletins, 1973 (Box 148, Folder 13)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- International Commission Newsletter, February 1981 (Box 148, Folder 14)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Lesbian and Gay Task Force Publications, circa 1972-1979 (Box 309, Folder 13)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Moving On -- Drafts, Correspondence, Research Materials, and Issues, 1973-1980 (Box 148, Folder 15, Box 309, Folder 14-17, Box 310, Folder 1-5, Box 311, Folder 1)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- New York and the Crisis of Our Cities, circa 1976 (Box 311, Folder 2)
  - New American Movement Newspaper, 1971-1978
    - Correspondence, Reports, and Issues, 1971-1974 (Box 149, Folder 1, Box 311, Folder 3)
    - Collective Meeting Minutes, Correspondence, and Reports, 1975 (Box 311, Folder 4)
    - Editorial Board Meeting Minutes, Reports, and Correspondence, 1976 (Box 311, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence and Resolutions, 1977-1978 (Box 311, Folder 6)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- The Organizer, 1976 (Box 311, Folder 7)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Organizing a Socialist Student Movement, 1974 (Box 311, Folder 8)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Pamphlets and Working Papers, 1971-1972 (Box 149, Folder 2, Box 311, Folder 9)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Pamphlets and Working Papers, 1973-1974 (Box 149, Folder 3, Box 312, Folder 1)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Pamphlets and Working Papers, 1975-1977 (Box 149, Folder 4, Box 312, Folder 2)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Pamphlets and Working Papers, 1979-1981 (Box 149, Folder 5, Box 312, Folder 3)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Smith, David N. with Dean Manders -- The Party and the Struggle for Consciousness, June 1975 (Box 312, Folder 4)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Plant Closings Bulletin, circa 1979-1981 (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Political Education Course Manuals, circa 1974-1976 (Box 150, Folder 1, Box 312, Folder 5, Box 343, Folder 8)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- The Political Perspective, 1972-1980 (Box 150, Folder 2, Box 312, Folder 6)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Reproductive Rights Newsletter, 1978-1979 (Box 312, Folder 7)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Boyte, Harry and Frank Ackerman -- Revolution and Democracy, circa 1973 (Box 312, Folder 8)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Socialist-Feminist Commission, 1972-1977
    - Socialism/Feminism Conference Papers, 1972 (Box 150, Folder 3)
    - Commission Publications, 1972-1977 (Box 312, Folder 9)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Songs and Songbook, undated (Box 312, Folder 10)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Ackerman, Frank and Harry Boyte -- Strategies for Change: The Marxist Tradition, circa 1974-1975 (Box 312, Folder 11)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- "A Study Packet", 1971 (Box 312, Folder 12)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Teacher Unionism, 1976 (Box 150, Folder 4, Box 312, Folder 13)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Tell It Like It Is, 1974-1975 (Box 312, Folder 14)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Undocumented Workers: Are They a Problem?, 1977 (Box 312, Folder 15)